Finding Aid for Robert R. McMath Papers 1916-1962
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Research and topical files
  - Newspaper clippings (Box 10)
Oct. 6, 1954; Oct. 26, 1954
Scripps, William Edmund, 1882-1952.
Apr.-June 1948 folder
Shapley, Harlow, 1885-
Nov. 7, 1941; Nov. 16, 1941; Dec. 17, 1941; Dec. 31, 1941; July 19, 1941; Oct. 30, 1942; Dec. 16, 1942; Aug. 10, 1943; Oct. 30, 1946; Nov. 6, 1946
Shirley, Joseph W.
Mar. 18, 1941; May 9, 1941; May 16, 1941; May 27, 1941; June 24, 1941
Smith, Shirley Wheeler, 1875-1959.
Oct. 19, 1935; Oct. 25, 1935; Nov. 13, 1937; Dec. 15, 1937; May 26, 1938; June 6, 1938; Dec. 28, 1938; June 4, 1940; June 6, 1940; June 19, 1940
Stason, E. Blythe (Edwin Blythe), 1891-1972.
July 12, 1943
Stebbins, Joel, 1878-
May 17, 1940; Oct. 14, 1940; Mar. 17, 1941; Apr. 4, 1941; May 23, 1941; May 28, 1941; June 5, 1941; Jan. 31, 1942; Apr. 29, 1942; Aug. 9, 1942; Apr. 18, 1943; May 23, 1943; Mar. 16, 1955
Stetson, Harlan True, 1885-1964.
Sept. 28, 1932; Oct. 13, 1932; Oct. 26, 1932; Nov. 8, 1932; Dec. 10, 1932; Dec. 20, 1932; Jan. 3, 1933; Feb. 6, 1933; Mar, 10, 1933; Jan. 12, 1939; Oct. 19, 1939; Nov. 16, 1939; Feb. 1, 1940; Aug. 28, 1940; Sept. 17, 1940; Oct. 14, 1940; Oct. 16, 1940; Nov. 4, 1940; Dec. 6, 1940; Dec. 13, 1940; Jan. 7, 1941; May 22, 1941; Aug. 19, 1941
Stone, Julius Frederick., 1855-1947.
May 29, 1937; Nov. 5, 1937; Jan. 13, 1939; Jan. 19, 1939; Jan. 27, 1939, Feb. 2, 1939; Mar. 11, 1939; Apr. 18, 1939; May, 16, 1939; May 24, 1939; June 14, 1939; July 11, 1939; July 24, 1939; Aug. 3, 1939; Aug. 18, 1939; Dec. 4, 1939; Dec. 11, 1939; Dec. 20, 1939; Jan. 5, 1940; Jan. 27, 1940; Apr. 13, 1940; Apr. 17, 1940; May 14, 1940; May 21, 1940; May 28, 1940; May 31, 1940; June 7, 1940; June 13, 1940; June 21, 1940; July 1, 1940; July 11, 1940; Nov. 4, 1940; Dec. 16, 1940; Feb. 7, 1941; Feb. 13, 1941; Feb. 17, 1941; Mar. 1, 1941; Mar. 13, 1941; Mar. 29, 1941; May 12, 1941; May 16, 1941; May 27, 1941; June 19, 1941; July 16, 1941; July 29, 1941; Aug. 25, 1941; Nov. 7., 1941; Nov. 10, 1941; Nov. 17, 1941; Dec. 4, 1941; Dec. 12, 1941; Jan. 5, 1942; Jan. 21, 1942; Jan. 23, 1942; Feb. 16, 1942; Mar. 3, 1942; Mar. 25, 1942; Apr. 13, 1942; Apr. 28, 1942; May 4, 1942; May 13, 1942; June 4, 1942; July 14, 1942; July 17, 1942; July 27, 1942; July 31, 1942; Feb. 17, 1943; Mar. 18, 1943; Mar. 25, 1943; Mar. 27, 1943; Apr. 2, 1943; Apr. 17, 1943; Apr. 23, 1943; May 14, 1943; June 25, 1943; Nov. 3, 1943, Jan. 4, 1944; Aug. 28, 1944; Sept. 5, 1944; Sept. 20, 1944; Oct. 2, 1944; Oct. 12, 1944; Oct. 26, 1944; Jan. 16, 1945; Feb. 27, 1945; Mar. 15, 1945; Mar. 20, 1945; June 10, 1945; Aug. 29, 1945; Sept 25, 1945; Oct. 1, 1945; Oct. 8, 1945; Nov. 14, 1945; Jan. 3, 1946; Mar. 5, 1946; Apr. 9, 1946; May 2., 1946; June 18, 1946; Oct. 8, 1946
Struve, Otto, 1897-1963.
Jan.-June 1950 folder; July-Dec. 1950 folder; and throughout AAS correspondence
Tapping, Theodore Hawley, 1889-1969.
May 25, 1933; June 1933
Waterman, Alan Tower, 1892-
June 25, 1957; Nov.-Dec. 1957
Whipple, Fred Lawrence, 1906-
Oct.-Dec. 1954 folder; July-Sept. 1955 folder
White, Alfred H. (Alfred Holmes), 1873-1953.
Jan. 12, 1933; Jan. 16, 1933; Mar. 1, 1933; Mar. 2, 1933; Mar. 16, 1933; Apr. 5, 1933; Oct. 5, 1938; Oct. 15, 1938; Oct. 19, 1938; Oct. 28, 1940; Feb. 25, 1946
Wilson, Charles Erwin, 1890-1961.
Dec. 21, 1955
Yoakum, Clarence Stone, 1879-1945.
Sept. 15, 1936; Mar. 25, 1937; Apr. 12, 1937; May 3, 1938; Nov. 7, 1938; Jan. 17, 1941; Dec. 7, 1942